bestslogans.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy

**With effect from: 1st January, 2017**

At Best Slogans, we take the privacy of our customers very seriously. We may ask you to provide personally identifiable information to access premium areas of our website or when requesting for a service. All information thus collected will be used strictly in accordance with the terms laid out in this privacy policy. 

Best Slogans reserves the right to update this policy from time-to-time without prior notice. It is your responsibility to read the policy periodically and take note of the changes. Continued use of the website, after policy updates, implies that you have read the revised statement and consent to the changes. 

**Information we collect:**   
It includes personally identifiable information such as:

* Name
* Designation
* Contact Information - Postal Address, Telephone Numbers and Email Address
* Demographic Information - Postcode, Preferences and Interests, IP addresses, Internet Browser, Pages viewed etc.

We also collect other information relevant to customer surveys and offers. 

**How do we use this information?**  
This information is important to internal record keeping. The primary purpose of collecting personally identifiable and demographic information is to improve our services by catering to the needs of website visitors, members and customers. We use it to enhance our products and services as well as make updates to our website. 

We might use this information for business promotion too, in sending you newsletters or emails informing you about new products and special interests if we think it might interest you. Occasionally, we may use the provided information for market research purposes too. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or email. 

**Data Protection**  
We institute special physical, electronic and managerial measures to protect private and confidential personal information by preventing unauthorized access. 

However, no security system is full-proof. We disclaim responsibility for any information lost, misused or corrupted as a result of an interception of our security systems. We shall also not be liable for data lost or corrupted during transit over the internet. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Best Slogans makes use of cookies. A cookie is a small text-only file that requests permission to be stored on the User's hard drive. Once stored on your hard drive, it keeps track of your internet activity. It analyses web traffic, or informs you when you visit a particular site etc. 

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. It creates for a more targeted web experience by customizing the operations to your needs, likes and dislikes as it records information of your preferences. Basically, a cookie does not allow unauthorized access to your computer or personal information, except for the information you volunteer to share. It helps us provide a better web experience to Users, by monitoring web page traffic, the web pages with maximum traffic as well as those that users don't find very useful. Information collected by cookies is strictly used for statistical analysis, after which it is permanently deleted from our systems. 

It is your decision to accept or decline cookies. You can opt out of using cookies by changing the settings in your browser. Disenabling cookies may restrict access to certain sections of the website. 

**Third Party Links**   
Our site contains links to related third party sites. We have no control over these sites and our privacy policy does not govern the exchange between you and these third party sites. We will not be responsible for the security of any personally identifiable information furnished to them. If you submit any kind of information, you do so at your own risk. As a precautionary measure, you should read the respective privacy statement. 

We also serve third party advertisements on our website. These companies often extract demographic information (not personally identifiable information such as name, postal address, telephone number or email address) concerning your web activity, for instance the websites you visit, to offer advertisements about goods and services that interest you. For more information on how these companies use this information and if you want to opt out of it, click here. 

**Controlling the Use of Information**  
As a website User you can fully control the collection and use of your personal information in the following ways:

* When asked to fill out a form on the website, you can deny permission to use your information for directing marketing purposes, by ticking the relevant box.
* If earlier you had agreed to the use of personal information for direct marketing purposes, you can always opt out of it later by writing to us or dropping an email.

No personal information is sold, leased or distributed to third parties without your written consent or unless required to do so by law. We use this information primarily to send you third party promotional content, that we think you may find interesting. 

Under the Data Protection Act of 1998, you can request to know the personal information we hold, use and share. We will provide these details for a small fee. You can request a copy of this information by sending us an email here. If any of the information is incorrect or incomplete, you are requested to notify us of the same by writing to us or emailing us here. We will update the information as soon as possible.

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.
